DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
Don't think it's a bit much?
How many guys did you bring
just to take me out?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
So, that's all you have to say
for your last words?
First, I'm going to prep two cameras.
You can install them
at the location I mentioned.
Okay. And then?
Then, my phone.
We install spyware on it
as insurance.
You know, a zombie phone.
Then I put an app on your spare phone
so you can remotely control my phone.
Even if my phone is turned off
we can tweak it so that certain
functions stay active like malware.
Audio and video recording
will still work.
Everything will auto-upload
to the cloud every 30 minutes
so it won't be tampered with.
This feels dangerous.
What are you planning that you need
to prepare this thoroughly?
Knowing too much will get you hurt.
This guy.
You think this is funny?
It is funny. You don't think so?
Hey.
Let's be real.
Can you actually kill me?
Do you have the guts
without your boss
Moon Do-hyuk, giving the order?
You're just his errand boy.
You must be desperate
to find a way out of this.
Forget it.
Mr. Moon already signed off on it.
Whether you die here
or vanish without a trace
it won't be a problem,
you piece of shit.
Take him out.
You scared me.
Because she's more likely to live
a normal life
through you, rather than me.
Tell me. What do you want me to do?
- Anything for you.
- If anything happens, call me.
Why not? Why won't you?
You could be in danger--
No. I don't want that.
Why do I have to suffer?
All right.
- I understand.
- So go ahead, Ah-jin.
Use me all you want.
That's what I want.
MESSAGES
KIM JAE-OH
CONFIRM
How many guys did you bring?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Check his phone.
YOON JUN-SEO
Have you finished the job?
As you can see, yes.
Make sure to clean it up
without a trace.
Do we get rid of this, too?
It's his phone.
You can give it to me.
I need to check it, just in case.
This psycho dragged the CEO's name
into his threats.
I need to see what he was holding.
Welcome home, ma'am.
CALLING
The phone you have dialed
is turned off.
You will be connected to voicemail
after the beep.
You will incur charges
once connected.
Press one to leave a message.
Press two to leave a callback number.
Your time to press a button
has expired.
Press one to leave a message.
Press two to leave a callback number.
Your time to press a button
has expired.
Press one to leave a message.
Press two to leave a callback number.
Please check the instructions
and call again.
Thank you for using our service.
Goodbye.
Take care of Kim Jae-oh
however you want.
Just make sure
I never hear about him again.
I don't want his name
ruining another meal with my wife.
EPISODE 12: THE FINAL X
Where's Kim Jae-oh?
Where is he?
I had no idea
what this job was for.
If I had known,
I never would have helped him.
What was it?
The cameras.
He asked me to install them
at the construction site.
He said the footage would auto-upload
and that I should collect the cameras
once enough time passed
and hand you
the memory card
and my spare phone.
What are you doing? Throw him.
Two of you stay on the lookout.
The rest go down and clean it up.
- Yes, sir.
I don't see anyone.
Even Ms. Gong stepped out.
I asked them to give us some privacy.
Sit. I have something to say.
I wonder
what you want to say to me.
From now on,
don't touch me without permission.
Don't hug me from behind
like earlier.
Don't even let your breath touch me.
Don't do anything.
That's unreasonable.
Aren't we husband and wife?
Because we're husband and wife
I'm telling you
not to treat me like a doll.
If I'm your wife
you should treat me as your equal.
Isn't that right?
I thought pitying you
and adoring you was enough.
Why should I listen to that?
I'm sure you received
the report by now.
I found a way to corner you.
People who got locked up
and disappeared on your orders.
Now, there's one more.
And I have the evidence.
Let's be real.
Can you actually kill me?
Do you have the guts
without your boss
Moon Do-hyuk, giving the order?
You're just his errand boy.
You must be desperate
to find a way out of this.
Forget it.
Mr. Moon already signed off on it.
Whether you die here
or vanish without a trace
it won't be a problem,
you piece of shit.
What are you doing?
Throw him.
You're not the only one
who can corner me or discard me.
With your perfect little life
a single crack will stand out.
Can you handle that?
Mr. Perfectionist?
So, this is what you wanted to say?
You made me sit here just for that?
When you gave the order
I was there.
The evidence is here.
And so is the witness.
I can't tell
if this is a negotiation or a threat.
Does your dear friend know
that his death
is being used like this?
He'd be proud
he was used for my sake.
It wasn't exploitation.
He let himself be used.
Just so I could have something
to shake you with
he risked everything.
You had everything from the beginning
so I wouldn't expect
you to understand.
What the heck did you do?
Say something.
If I tell you
can you handle it?
Tell me.
I wanted to put a leash
around Do-hyuk's neck.
So he couldn't mess with me again.
And Jae-oh helped me do that.
He walked straight in
knowing that he'd die.
That's what he wanted.
What are you trying to say?
You did nothing wrong,
whether Jae-oh is dead or not?
- That--
- What should I have done, then?
How long are you
going to live like that?
I'm sick of it, too.
Jun-seo.
Now that Jae-oh ended up like that
I can't stop anymore.
Is this all my fault?
Who has the right to condemn me?
Who can understand
my situation and my position
right now?
Then, answer me this one thing.
You can stop now.
This is the end, right?
Right?
Please say something.
Please tell me that this is the end!
I can't stop.
I won't stop.
If you knew how dangerously
I'm hanging on to this position
you wouldn't tell me to stop.
This is Yoon Jun-seo.
Does the documentary offer
from last time
still stand?
Hold on, sir. How can I help you?
- What's the matter?
- Moon Do-hyuk.
Mr. Yoon Jun-seo?
I didn't think
you'd come find me in person.
You killed Jae-oh.
Everything you ordered is
all recorded here.
I see.
And?
If you're planning
to do anything to Ah-jin
I'll spread this footage
to the media.
A lot of people are telling me
what to do today.
But tell me.
Do you think I'll just sit still
while you post that?
I'm sure you know I can do
far more than you can.
A cheap video
where my name is barely mentioned
won't...
- Do we get rid of this, too?
- What's this?
It's his phone.
You can give it to me.
This psycho dragged the CEO's name
into his threats.
Anyway, once this is handled properly
put in a good word for me
with Mr. Moon.
I still feel uneasy
about that mistake last time.
The fire incident, right?
If we had killed him properly then,
we wouldn't have had to do this.
Perhaps releasing the video
and audio recordings I have
won't deal a fatal blow to you.
But you know what?
It'll leave a stain.
Once those stains pile up
the perfect reputation
you've been keeping so far
will get dirty eventually.
I can always clean up
when things get dirty.
But are you threatening me right now?
I'm here to warn you.
Because I can't just sit by and watch
you or Ah-jin any longer.
Now that I think about it
your friend also tried to warn me,
and we both know how he ended up.
I guess friends
share similar traits.
Leave Ah-jin alone.
I'll be the one to stop her.
You just take a step back
and watch from afar.
Just like you always have.
I've come to make a confession.
Sister, I know
who killed your family.
It's someone you know.
Actress Baek Ah-jin
invited to the Berlin Film Festival
with The Woman with a Suitcase
is making a strong impression
internationally.
Through her recent film
Amen to Nothing
Baek Ah-jin has captivated
critics and audiences
with a bold transformation
and a fully immersive performance.
Many say that she's at the peak
of her acting career.
Tonight at the Bluedragon Awards
she's considered the strongest
candidate for Best Actress.
Will she take home the award
at the Bluedragon Awards tonight?
All eyes are on her.
- Why are you glowing so much today?
- You look stunning.
It's the same face you see every day.
What's the fuss?
And it's pretty every day.
I can never get tired of your beauty.
I agree.
JUN-SEO
You can just leave that.
I can throw it out for you.
- I'll--
- No.
It's okay. I'll throw it out.
Oh, sure.
BAEK AH-JIN
If you ever feel like helping me,
call me then.
Otherwise, don't get in my way
for no reason.
It's Baek Ah-jin!
You're aware the award show is airing
on a different channel now, right?
They say the Best Actress Award is
basically guaranteed to go to her.
That actually works out better.
Because her final appearance
will stay in people's memories
as her most beautiful one.
DIM HEART: TWO FACES OF AN ACTRESS
NOTABLE TRAITS:
ANTISOCIAL PERSONALITY DISORDER
FOUND IN ABOUT 4 PERCENT
OF THE POPULATION
Baek Ah-jin.
She falls within the four percent
of the population
with antisocial personality disorder.
She views others as tools
and manipulates or uses them
to achieve her goals.
At the biggest annual event
in Korean cinema
Baek Ah-jin stands
as a top contender for Best Actress
drawing intense attention
from media and fans alike.
She has never
physically committed murder
but she caused
the deaths of two people.
She has deliberately approached
only men who were of use to her.
She still harbors
an unfulfilled plan to kill.
She is Baek Ah-jin, an actress.
Now, let us begin
the 46th Bluedragon Awards.
Let's get started.
Baek Ah-jin is
the strongest candidate
for Best Actress, right?
If she wins, ratings will explode.
Don't tell her anything beforehand.
Make sure no one gets near her.
Got it?
...Song Kyeong-su.
DIM HEART
Baek Ah-jin.
The elegant and kind actress.
Baek Ah-jin?
She was the epitome of perfection.
She was smart, kind, and pretty.
She stood out wherever she was.
Everyone at our school knew her.
Even the teachers adored her.
But those who knew her well
tell a completely different story.
We met those people.
What do I think of Baek Ah-jin?
A devil wearing human skin.
She didn't have a mother.
And her father was a criminal.
She wasn't normal,
at least from what I felt.
It always seemed like her emotions
were rehearsed, as if she was acting.
Her acting has
always been exceptional.
She switched masks
whenever it suited her needs.
That's why I could never tell
what she was thinking.
I think she has
very little empathy for others.
I figured that was the case.
I even recommended
she get psychological counseling.
TRUE LOVE COUNSELING CENTER
Check this out.
It's about Baek Ah-jin.
Is this for real?
Isn't she terrifying?
How can a human being do this?
Now, we'll move on to the highly
anticipated Best Actress Award.
Last year's winner, Jin Seo-gyeong,
will be joining us to present it.
Please give her a round of applause.
Hello, I'm Jin Seo-gyeong.
Let me announce the winner.
The Best Actress Award
at the 46th Bluedragon Awards...
goes to...
Baek Ah-jin for Amen to Nothing.
Congratulations.
Baek Ah-jin,
the winner of the Best Actress Award
portrayed a nun in Amen to Nothing
who investigates the tragedy
that befell her family
and carries out revenge
delivering a deeply moving
and introspective performance
about a character
in anguish over religious doubts.
Congratulations
from the bottom of our hearts.
Thank you.
First of all
my mom
in heaven.
How do I look, Mom?
Are you proud of me?
Her mother died in an accident.
Her father was
the victim of a murder case.
She was also present
at her lover's grandmother's death
and later, her lover took
his own life.
For one person
to experience all of this
the coincidences seem too extreme.
- A documentary about Ah-jin is out.
- What?
That's a scoop.
Start preparing for revisions.
- Check if any articles are out.
- Yes, sir.
While working on Amen to Nothing
I couldn't help but wonder...
"Where is my God?"
Looking back
I realized
He was inside me all along.
I grew up
in an unfortunate environment.
But luck always followed me.
I thought we were incredibly lucky.
I caught myself wondering
if she was an angel
who had come down for my brother.
But I overheard something
at my grandma's funeral.
Was it someone in the film industry?
Apparently, she was smiling
in front of him.
Every step I took to get here
wasn't easy.
But I never stopped.
I kept moving forward
and eventually, I got here.
Her acting has
always been exceptional.
She switched masks
whenever it suited her needs.
To everyone who walked with me
on my journey to today
I offer my sincere gratitude.
She used the people around her
to make me look
like an idiot and a thief.
Could she have used our boss
to try to kill her own father?
We were like family
when she was dating my brother.
I thought she'd at least
show up once at the funeral.
I was stunned.
Soon after, news came out
that she was marrying a chaebol.
I was like, "What?"
These testimonies about Baek Ah-jin
are not easy to verify.
So, we wondered
whether continuing this investigation
was the right thing to do.
Then, we learned something new.
Rumors surrounding
the suspicious death of her father,
Baek Seon-gyu.
Dim Heart began to track down
the truth of that day.
There were three primary suspects
in this case.
Former baseball player, Mr. Choi.
And the person who was
consistently abused by the victim
and thus had the clearest motive,
the victim's daughter
actress Baek Ah-jin
BAEK AH-JIN
ANTISOCIAL PERSONALITY DISORDER
I remember that case.
It was very unusual.
There was only one victim
but multiple potential perpetrators.
Among them, the one
with the clearest motive was
the victim's daughter, Baek Ah-jin.
Lastly
to everyone
who loved my performance
and showed enthusiasm for my work
and to those who supported me
not only as an actress
but as a person.
I give this glory to you.
I sincerely thank you.
The final suspect provided
our team with a decisive tip.
It was Yoon Seok-ha,
the author of Co-Offender Y.
The incident back then
was planned from the beginning.
It's true that Ah-jin
deliberately sought out
someone kind enough to act for her.
It's also true that
she found Choi Jung-ho and used him.
It would have been easy for her
to win someone over
and set a trap.
Back then
she even had a stalker decoy to use.
When the said stalker hit her,
she immediately called Mr. Choi
so he rushed over.
But it wasn't a stalker.
The person Choi struck
with the bat was...
Seeing you alive
wasn't part of my plan.
...the man disguised
to look like her stalker.
It was her father
Baek Seon-gyu.
When I arrived, Choi was already gone
and Baek Seon-gyu
was lying on the floor.
There was blood everywhere
so I assumed he was dead.
Then, I saw Ah-jin.
She was sitting
against the bathroom wall
holding the bat.
She looked at me and said
"It's over."
That's what she said.
"It's all over."
Other people's suffering
meant nothing to her.
She only ever used people
to achieve her own goals
and discarded them.
That's how she built...
her current position.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Anywhere
without people.
I thought you'd change
if I waited long enough.
But you didn't.
I realized that far too late.
That I couldn't save you
and that I was clinging
to something impossible.
That you could never change.
Exactly.
And you realized
that simple thing too late.
So what? Do you regret it now?
No.
Because now,
I'm the only one who can handle you.
Handle me how?
I have nowhere to go anymore.
If you truly have nowhere to go
how about we go to hell together
Ah-jin?
Are you being serious?
I already decided
to stay with you to the end.
If you stop now
I'll stop, too.
What will you do?
I thought there was nothing left
that could tie me down.
But it was you.
My final shackle.
Let's not do anything anymore.
So that no one gets hurt
we'll only look at each other.
I love you...
Ah-jin.
Last night, the car driven
by author Yoon Seok-ha
crashed into a guardrail
and fell off a cliff.
The driver, Yoon Seok-ha,
died at the scene
and actress Baek Ah-jin,
believed to be the passenger
is currently missing.
The police are investigating
the exact cause of the accident.
WRITER YOON SEOK-HA DEAD,
ACTRESS BAEK AH-JIN MISSING
At some point
your presence started feeling
like a blade stuck in my heart.
Even in death, I wouldn't be able
to understand or forgive you.
So, in this life, I wanted to cleanly
sever anything tied to you and leave.
And I wanted to disappear
from your life, too.
That's the best choice.
I gave you
one last brief moment of happiness
so you can live
the rest of your life
with that in mind.
Maybe this is
the first and last long revenge
I'll ever give you, Mom.
No, Jun-seo.
Jun-seo.
I hope you stay healthy.
Jun-seo!
You can't find her anywhere?
No signs of life or trace anywhere?
Fine, never mind.
You don't have to go that far.
ACTRESS BAEK AH-JIN STILL MISSING
Just leave the broadcast
and respond
when they ask for cooperation.
We want to share
a follow-up to our previous broadcast
"Two Faces of an Actress."
We recently learned that Yoon Jun-seo
our informant
and the author of Co-Offender Y
passed away not long ago.
Please pay attention to this video.
It was submitted anonymously.
This footage proves
that she was in the vehicle
that Yoon Jun-seo was driving.
After this video,
she vanished completely
and has not been reachable since.
THE LATE BAEK AH-JIN
Do something about this!
Subtitles by Ho-young Yun